Previously...
..on Love Island...
..there was a day of drama
in paradise...
Wes deserves better than her.
Laura says
Wes deserves better than you.
..and four more islanders
were dumped.
The boy I want to couple up with
is Sam.
Meg.
Tonight...
I am done with Georgia.
..a stolen kiss causes conflict.
He came to kiss me.
Go away. Go away.
I will tell you something right now.
if I find out
that he went in and kissed her.
then I am done.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
After Adam. Alex. Darylle and Ellie
faced the dramatic dumping.
the remaining islanders
are all thinking the same thing -
Loose Women are going to need
a bigger desk!
Don't cry. Don't feel bad.
You made the right decision.
Don't get upset. Come here.
You had to do what you had to do.
babe. please don't get upset.
Today was the single hardest day
of my whole Love Island experience.
period.
I'm so sorry.
Hey. don't.
Ellie. we have got a past.
but I want her to be happy.
I want her to find someone.
Unfortunately it weren't here.
but I honestly do wish her
the best of luck in life.
I know it is only a week. but...
you're something else.
He was a proper man. he had his shit
together. he respected me.
he was always there.
I will miss him massively.
I am so sad. though.
It has been a journey.
I am really going to miss Adam.
He's an absolute softy.
Behind those tattoos and muscles
he is an absolute gem of a guy.
I love him to bits.
He's like a brother to me
and it feels like a brother is going
home. to be honest.
I really mean that.
I am going to miss Adam so much.
He hasn't been the same
since Zara left.
I think he has proved everybody
wrong.
Sammy. are you all right?
Come here.
I'm not all right at all.
Like. I don't know why.
My time in the villa has been
absolutely phenomenal.
I have loved
every single minute of it.
And I think it is probably the right
time to go for me. if I am honest.
I have broken a few hearts in here
but I am really looking forward
to trying to see Zara
and see how that goes.
because that is definitely one
I am not wanting
to break any time soon.
ALL: Bye!
Love yous all.
It's a very sad moment.
But on the bright side. we kept
the receipts for those extra beds
we bought so we can get
our money back. Every cloud. eh?
Meg. Congratulations.
Megan's relieved about being saved.
but she is still angry after
finding out a certain air hostess
has been flying off at the mouth.
Apparently. Laura has been saying
you deserve better than me.
She has never said that to me.
She said that to Alex -
"I don't know why Wes is interested.
he deserves better than Megan."
Give me a kiss.
Try and keep a cool head.
Laura.
Laura. Can I speak to you?
Yeah. of course.
I think what Laura has said
is out of order.
Bang out of order to say
that Megan doesn't deserve me.
What's that all about?
Alex said whilst we were on the
date. you and Alex had a chat
and apparently you said to him.
"Wes deserves better than Megan."
Yeah. I did.
It really shocked me.
At the end of the day.
the way I see it
is anyone that goes back to an ex...
It is not an ex. How is that an ex?
I got to know the boy
for one day romantically.
Wes has left. you've kissed
two boys. got with Alex.
you're not sure about Wes.
you're back and forth.
I don't agree with that.
I don't think
that someone that
has been (BLEEP) off by someone else
should go back there.
I had a day with the boy and then
another guy came in.
I spent three days with him. Of
course I'll have a better connection
with the guy I had three days with.
No. not necessarily.
If you went on a date...
That is my opinion.
You're good enough for him. I'm not?
It's got nothing to do with me.
In what sense
does he deserve better?
I have constantly bit my tongue
and now I am being told
to bite it even more.
No. I have an opinion.
Why act like my friend...
Why act like my friend
and then try to get with the guy I
am seeing? Don't double standard me.
Shh!
What you did to me...
You acted like we were fine...
No. Megan. Exactly. we were friends.
What you did to me
was ten times worse. OK?
How is it?
Megan. you went behind my back.
I said to Wes. "Are you happy
with Laura or not?"
He said no. So then we cracked on.
Megan. Megan.  Yeah.
We were friends.
you went behind my back
to the guy I was seeing for three
weeks and told him you fancied him.
then pursued him.
The day I was still kissing him.
You were wearing my shoes that
night. Please don't patronise me.
"Wearing my shoes"?
She did run up on you
in Laura's shoes.
I really don't care.
it was a passing comment.
It is nothing to do with me.
It is a passing comment?
I just think you should have said
it to me first.
rather than saying to Alex.
who I was coupled up with.  OK.
If I am asked an opinion...
I don't really care.
Don't speak to me
like a piece of shit.
You are a piece of shit.
You are such a dick. Wow.
I will go and get Laura now.
Laura. Laura.
Oh. my God.
Is she serious?
What was that about?
She came up to me and said.
"Why are you saying that Wes
deserves better than me?"
saying that I am belittling her.
I said. "Megan. I don't agree
with the way you have played it."
If someone screws someone over.
I don't think they should go back
there. That is what I said.
Come here.
I don't know who she thinks she is
to start saying that.
I still think she does have feelings
for Wes. and she's hurt about that.
Why do she care so much?
She should be happy with Jack.
Focus on your own relationship.
Why is she so concerned with Wes?
I don't have time
for people like that.
Laura's night is only going
to get worse
cos Jack is telling her
about his date with Georgia.
I reckon the scales
will fall from Laura's eyes.
which is impressive cos
they're stuck on with superglue.
Don't get me wrong.
it was a nice date. a good date.
G is attractive. I am not denying
that. she's fit.
But I don't really see it working
with me and her.
I did make that kind of clear.
But then when we got up to leave.
I've gone in for a kiss on the cheek
kind of thing.
and she has come in towards me
straight on and kissed me
on the lips.
So you kissed on the lips?
Yeah.
Not intentionally. but yeah.
She has gone for a two kiss thing.
I pulled away the second time
because I thought.
this is so not what I need
right now.
With the situation with the kiss.
we said goodbye. I went to kiss her
on the cheek.
she kind of turned a little bit so I
did end up kissing her on the lips.
She tried to kiss me a little bit
again and I backed out a bit
because my loyalties lie with Laura.
If you look at the absolute facts.
OK. me and G have kissed
on the lips.
but if you look at the whole
spectrum of it in context.
you will understand that is not
the case and it wasn't intentional.
Don't think anything of it.
No. I don't.
But what you have got to understand
from my side.
it is difficult now because
I know that Georgia fancies you
and she has tried to kiss you.
But that is when
you have to trust me.  I do.
Good. Now it is just a discussion
between you and her.
All right? Give me a kiss.
Georgia. are you serious?
She has tried to kiss him
at the end of the date.
She told me two seconds
before she went on the date
she didn't fancy the boy.
I am done with Georgia.
Oh. my God. I have massively
been there for her.
but she is actually a little girl
and I don't rate her as a person
any more.
Come on. then.
Get it all out to me. babe.
otherwise it boggles at your brain.
I want it all out. everything.
I think you should go first.
it is your date.
It was nice. I spoke to you
beforehand. we got on.
I thought he was funny.
He told me his loyalties
lay with you. I said "great".
"Do you see a relationship with
Laura?" He went. "It's early days."
I said. "The reason I took you out
is because at the moment
I thought. who can make me laugh
right now?
Who can I have banter with?
Who can I chill with right now?"
But I said. "However. my loyalties
lie with Laura
because she is one of my best
friends in this villa
and I ain't going to jeopardise
that ever."
So you didn't try and kiss him
at the end of the date?
We kissed each other. yeah.
He tried to kiss you on the cheek
goodbye
and you went in for the lips twice?
That is an absolute lie.
He told me that you tried to kiss
each other goodbye on the cheek
and you went in for the lips.
he pulled away. and you went
in again for the lips.
That is an absolute lie.
It is not like I insinuated it.
You both went in at the same time
and kissed on the lips?  Yeah.
We said goodbye. the date went well.
and I said. "Bye-bye. babe."
It was a kiss on the lips.
You think that is normal.
to kiss your mate's guy on the lips?
Again. my mate.
actually my best mate.
has gone behind my back
and tried to snog the guy
I am coupled up with.
All you say is that you have got
loyalties.  Which I do.
Your best mate's guy.
telling me it was purely
because you thought he made you
laugh.
Then all of a sudden you fancy him.
you have a connection.
you try to kiss him.
Now you are denying
trying to kiss him.
basically calling him a liar.
Let's get Jack over here right now.
then.
Let me ask you one more question...
Jack!
She sat in front of us today and
said she was a very loyal person.
as she always says.
knowing that she had kissed him.
Why sit there and bullshit?
She is a dickhead.
I do not like the girl.
She changes her morals
to match what she's doing.
Basically. Laura just told me
I tried to kiss you twice.
That is not the case. Jack. at all.
Hold on. I said.
that you both went in
for a kiss on the cheek.
No. you just said to me that you -
Georgia. don't fucking lie now.
No. you said to me -
You just called him a liar.
Do not tell me I am lying.
Laura. do not...
Georgia. wind your neck in.
Let me talk.
Why do you think I kissed you
on the lips after the date?
Because we did.
We did not.
What do you mean. we did not?
You can lie as much as you want.
We did not kiss on the lips
on purpose.
Oh. my God.
You did it.
Unintentionally.
we kissed on the lips. Agreed?
OK.  After that kiss. you went
for another little kiss
and I backed away.  OK.
If you didn't feel that or see that.
I don't know why.  OK.
She ain't going to trust me now.
that's fine.
I've told her how I feel.
Why would I. G?
Because I am your mate. Laura.
you have known me longer than him.
Georgia said how loyal she is
and how she only thought about
Laura.
yet didn't once mention
she had actually kissed him.
And I am just like.
practise what you preach. Georgia.
like. you are only as loyal
as your actions are.
Just saying you are loyal 20
times a day doesn't make you loyal.
It is bullshit.
Ellie. you need to pipe down.
Ellie. shut the fuck up.
Don't say how fucking loyal you are
when you are a liar.
Fucking hell.
Oh. don't chase me.
what are you going to do?
Shut up.
Fuck off.
Fucking ugly (BLEEP).
ALEX: That's very mature as well.
She's a fucking liar.
Still to come. the gloves are off.
Two people kiss for a reason.
You can blame one person...
I am so done.
Dan. you are being a dick.
Oh. flames. Nice symbolism.
because everybody is arguing
and stuff. Very arty.
It's all happening
because Georgia said
Jack went in for a smooch
on their date.
I don't think Georgia is a liar.
Jack has pulled in to kiss her.
I reckon he has. Wes.
I was there.  Did he kiss her?
I was there!
I watched the fucking thing.
What happened?
They kissed each other.
They fucking kissed each other!
It's a kiss.
She put it on him?
She probably was the one that...
They kissed each other! You can't...
Well. I'm going
to get up and tell him that then.
Listen. Dan. Come on.
No. I will say.
I don't care if she's leant in
or he's leant in.
they've kissed each other.
Listen. listen. listen!
I'm going to be honest. It weren't
just fucking one-sided with George.
So. it ain't fair.
It weren't one-sided. They wanted
to kiss each fucking other.
They wanted to kiss each other.
Who. me?  What the fuck. Dan!
They did want to kiss each other!
Wes. Wes! Stand at the front. now.
Me? I'm not fucking pointing fingers
at anyone.
Yes. she may have instigated it.
she may have started it.
but if you kiss someone.
you kiss each other.
I am not saying that
you are fucking wrong for doing it.
I'm not saying Georgia's wrong.
I'm not gonna bite.
I am not biting.  They have kissed.
Don't fucking
make me look like a mug.
Say what you have got to say.
I've got nothing to say.
I've told the truth.
You need to say something.
When. obviously.
I can see what is going on.
She's kissed you.
you've kissed her.
That was fucking -
No. let's get this straight
cos we all fucking live together.
We all talk.
Jack has told me that he went to
kiss her on the cheek and she moved.
And he pulled back.
This is the truth.
So. I'm sorry. I don't care if
anyone kisses anyone on the cheek.
If someone moves
and they accidentally kiss.
I fucking believe it.
And that's fair enough.
I said Georgia's instigated it.
Two people kiss for a reason.
You can't sit there
and blame one person.  Dani!
Two people kiss for a reason. Laura!
Then she shouldn't have said
how loyal she is to Laura.
I'm so done. Dan. you're fucking
being a dick.
Everyone always gets involved
with everyone's situation in here.
But. oh. my God.
choose your battles.
Like. if you don't know
and you weren't there.
then why would you think
you would know?
Why is everyone ganging up on her?
Boys as well?
It's not fair. everyone on one girl!
Everyoone's having a go at her.
Sorry. Ellie. saying
ugly (BLEEP) That's fucking low.
Alex. I got into a heated argument
with her
and she called me just as much.
It is out of order.
you have got to accept that.
We both called each other.
She's probably in the wrong. but you
should not call her an ugly (BLEEP).
I just don't like name-calling.
I don't care who was right.
Ellie shouldn't have said that.
I can certainly say that Georgia is
not ugly and she is not a C word.
Listen. listen. we're all fucking
adults. It's done now.
It's done. We don't need to be told
what to do and what not to do.
How old are you?
You are fucking adults.
You don't need to tell people
not to say something.
In the heat of the moment. she
said something. you said something.
We've all done some dumb shit.
It's fucking dead. It's done.
Exactly.
Where the fuck has that come from?
All this drama. all this madness
is only between two people.
A lot of speculation is going on.
Speculation equals nonsense.
Fucking hell. what is going on?
I am going to have something to eat.
In these sorts of times.
you have to eat something.
I think we need to go to bed.
My mum always says
never go to sleep on an argument.
which is why this
lot are still awake at 5:00am.
At least Laura has taken a break
from screaming at Georgia.
so she can have another go at Megan.
I never said you are not a fucking
better human than anyone else.
I wasn't comparing you to anyone.
As long as you and Laura are sweet.
it doesn't matter.
I am not nervous. you cannot bend
the truth. The truth is the truth.
No. you're not.
What are you leaving for
when you have got me?
Guys. let me just say one thing.
I am not condoning what I said.
She has been annoying.
She probably is in the wrong.
But you cannot lose it in
that way.
No one in the villa
wouldn't react...
I wouldn't say what you said.
And that's fine. but I do.
Ellie. you have far too much to say
about a lot of people here.
Go away. Go away.
Georgia is the only...
You can't say that.
Go away.
So why not voice it?
You have got a choice. Megan.
Did I lie to you? No.
I'd admit it straightaway.
I've got nothing to hide.
I don't care. Dan.
It's you. That's great...
Everyone is.
It's not everyone in the villa?
A few girls? You care about that?
You are just trying to worm your way
around. I am not interested.
I feel sick. I'm going to bed. mate.
(WHISPERING)
# I need to get some sleep.
I can't get no sleep #
Yesterday evening. Laura kicked off
at one girl and then another girl
and had a go at her fella.
Or. as they call it in Scotland.
a quiet night in with your mates.
What a fucking night. honestly.
Are you upset?
I feel like all my mates
have just gone against me.
Woah. You know things are serious
when they start talking in subtitles.
Ellie said some things
that we sadly couldn't subtitle
for legal reasons.
I shouldn't have said what I said.
People are just fixated on what I
said and not the reasons why.  Yeah.
I'll never be friends with her.
ever. Just keep my distance.
I am obviously full of regret
and I probably
said a few things
that I didn't mean.
However. I don't really want
to speak to Georgia today.
She is not someone
I want in my life.
I just want to keep our distance
and move on with my time in here.
I don't need to waste any more
energy on that girl.
because I don't like her.
I feel like Laura is scared
to be alone in this villa.
It's not as hard as you think.
but some people are
stronger than others.
I am very relieved
that Georgia saved me.
With everything that happened last
night. she's feeling a bit sad.
Now we are coupled up.
I can be that friend
to help her through it.
I really wanted Jack
to fucking comfort me in bed.
and he was like. "It's too much.
I need to sleep."
"Mate. I just stuck up for you
and believed you over Georgia.
and being attacked by the Megan
thing. can you just give me a hug?"
Jack. give me a break.
I can't remember a kiss causing
this much trouble
since I snogged
Annie Brown when we both had braces.
A firemen had to cut us free.
I'll be honest with you. babe.
He was quite forward with me.
I know he was.  Very forward.
OK? I ain't gonna lie.
No. I know you're not a liar.
It was a kiss. Dan.
I don't really think much of it.
if I'm honest.  No.
Anyway. Laura went.
"I think you're lying.
you're a liar!"
She called me a liar. Dan.
It all fucking kicked off
in the kitchen.
All I saw was red when I
saw everyone talking about you.
They are saying. "Apparently.
Georgia has leant in for the kiss."
I saw you walking past and everyone
is on you.  Why? What I done wrong?
LAURA: It's just a bit fake
sometimes. Do you know what I mean?
She is fake. though.
I do like Georgia.
I thought she was fucking my new
best mate. And then she fucking...
Yeah.
And then Ellie. out of nowhere.
babe. Ellie.
She has obviously called you...
I don't want to repeat it.
Blah blah blah.
I thought she was a friend in here.
I let her wear my clothes.
I help her out.
Why is she getting involved?
Thank you. Why?
She was in the kitchen watching
the show Jack put on
that was an absolute lie.
And basically sat there and got
involved. And said I wasn't loyal.
How have I not been loyal?
I was thinking. "You spiteful girl."
That is nasty.
Initially. it just started out when
I was trying to defend you
and how she actually sat there and
said she was loyal and everything.
It just got overheated. I got so
emotional. I just ended up. like...
I do honestly appreciate it.
Thank you so much.
Everyone knew he was lying. George.
That is where he has mugged himself
off here.
We know he was lying.
You're not a liar.
Why would you lie?
The truth comes out in the end.
I'm just going to continue
to be that way.
If people don't like it. then...
they can fuck off.
Yeah.
Still to come...
Charlie has a word.
If you initiate a conversation.
you look like the bigger person.
Fucking immature.
It looks like we will never know
whether Georgia tried to kiss Jack
or not.
(COUGHS)
It's all on camera.
But when it comes to G.
where is Sam's head at?
Would you say that you like her?
Like. like her?
Like. like her. or like her?
Do you know what I mean?
You know when you
just fancy someone. like.
you know I mean?
Yeah. I think I do. Yeah.
It's the first bird you've had here
that you gel with and like.
You've not really had that yet.
have you?
She has got like the two things.
With Samira. it was like
funny. laughs. we got on...
But you didn't really fancy her?
Like "Get in that bed!"
I did fancy Ellie. but. obviously.
that was it. Georgia has got...
A bit of both. You fancy her and
she's got a lot of personality.
For me. Georgia was always
my golden ticket.
When I came in. I fancied her.
I didn't think it'd happen.
Now we're coupled up
and getting on really well.
I really fancy her.
After the events of last night.
Megan is back with Wes and she
realised that when looking for love.
she shouldn't have gone
to SpecSavers.
Today. I do feel like
I'm happy and content.
I didn't walk in the villa thinking.
"I really fancy Wes."
The more time
you get to know someone
and their personality - he's fucking
gorgeous. He is so good-looking.
Is there a difference when you get
into bed. between Alex and Wes?
Yeah.
Good question.  100%.
With Alex. I know it sounds really
bad.
but before I got into bed with Alex.
I would see Wes and just
linger around like a lost puppy.
You would actually!  "Anything you
want to say before I get into bed?"
With Wes.
I am just like jumping in.
I can't help
but be like over the moon.
I am so happy
that me and Wes coupled up.
We haven't spent loads of time
together in a romantic way.
After that date. it confirmed to me
that I have made the right choice
and I won't be jumping ship again.
It just feels so natural.
I could tell him anything.
Even though I've effectively spent
two days with him romantically.
I feel like
we've been together for weeks.
I just want to hug him and when
I feel shit. I just. I dunno...
That's nice.
It's just natural.
I'm happy.
Good.
I am so happy that Megs and Wes
can have a second chance.
A second go at things.
It was all a bit messy.
Alex came and her head
was a bit twisted.
I think her head
is very free and clear
and she has finally got
what she wanted...
Mes. Mes! That is cute.
Last night. potty mouth Ellie used
language that was beneath the show
and I'd like to assure viewers
that it won't happen again.
because it was (BLEEP) disgraceful.
And Charlie agrees.
Obviously. it's difficult for me.
I have only known Ellie like a week.
I think she was over the top.
I have only seen her nice side.
She has very strong opinions about
things that she is not involved in.
They should apologise
to one another.  Agreed.
I'm going to have a chat with her.
for the boy's sake as well.
I don't want to be stuck in the
middle.  No. you don't.
Whether she'll listen or not.
I dunno.
Ellie is only 20.
I'm only three years older. but
there is a big maturity gap there.
I think there
is a big maturity gap there.
When people start calling
people names
and saying horrible things.
I draw the line. to be honest.
I don't think
there was any need for that.
I know a lot of the boys
feel the same.
When you kick off like that.
it looks bad on me. I defend you.
Obviously. you have your reasons
for kicking off.
You two should have a chat.
You should.
No. she's putting the full
situation. blaming it fully on me.
Yes. but you need to have a chat
and get your point across.
What are you going to do?
I'm not going to do anything.
You're not?
I can only give you advice. It is up
to you whether you want to take it.
Don't do that. I am just saying...
If you initiate the conversation.
you look like the bigger person.
You said something
you probably wished you hadn't.
in the heat of the moment.
Fucking immature.
I shouldn't have got as heated as
I did. but I stand by the reasons.
I think. to look in someone's eyes
and say you're loyal
when you have tried to kiss the
person they are seeing is bullshit.
Not knowing if Georgia made the first
move on Jack is driving them mad.
They should have watched
the show like everyone else!
I just don't think she would lie.
I might be wrong.
I don't know.
I wish I was there to confirm. I'm
just thinking why would Georgia lie?
To cover her own back.
She wants to be my mate.
It's fine.
It's not.
Why does it need to happen?
It's not like they sat and snogged.
I am just upset.
I feel like I have lost a best mate
in Georgia. which I really valued.
She kissed the guy I started seeing.
I didn't want that to happen.
Don't be negative. please.
It is hard not to.
I am taking control
of the situation
because I'm not having someone else
control how I feel.
I just think that Laura needs to
have a bit more trust in Georgia.
I know when you hear something about
a boy you like and someone you know
and if you know
that something has happened.
you might want to believe the boy.
Realistically. I don't think
your friend will lie.
I am going to stick by Georgia.
I do think she's telling the truth.
I don't think she would have
any gain in lying about that.
I will have to fight her corner
until everyone believes her.
Obviously. last night was shit.
We got into bed
and I had a hard night.
I don't know why you just rolled
over and went to sleep.
didn't try to comfort me.
I thought it was a bit shit.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry if you felt like
I wasn't there for you.
I was really tired.
Desperately tired.
I am just fed up
being nice and getting shat on.
I was upset last night and I wanted
Jack to kind of console me a bit.
And he didn't. really. I just
feel a bit vulnerable. I guess.
I have told you that I like you.
I fancy you.
I'm getting to know you
every day and I'm enjoying it.
But there has never been a time when
you've said. "Jack. I like you."
It only comes out of your mouth
when I have to ask you.
So what you insinuating?
I am asking. why is it
taking so long to tell me?
I'm trying to be chilled
for once in my life.
I don't want to tell you I like you
and you go off with someone else.
If anything. yesterday's date
solidified that that's not the case.
If I wanted to kiss Georgia.
I would have.
Jack is great. I just
feel like it is tainted a bit.
I hate when that happens.
I am sorry
that I didn't cuddle you in bed
and didn't console you and make you
feel like everything is OK.
Sorry. I'm just not very good
at this.
Neither am I.
I'm crap. Terrible. Shocking.
All right? Give me some shugs.
All right?
Coming up. The islanders shake
their bootys.
In my experience. there are two
ways to resolve conflict.
Sit people around the table.
or stick them in sexy costumes
and make them wiggle their bums
in each other's faces.
I'm thinking method two.
I got a text!
I am shit at dancing.
I can't dance. I can floss.
Get a good look.
It is all about the hips. Like that.
Like that.
Brace yourself. it is time
for the dirty dancing challenge.
The team that raises
the other team's heart rate the most
wins. First up is Kaz.
I feel so nervous.
Hopefully we can pull together
and get the hearts beating
really fast.
Wow. wow. wow.
Sorry. dad. Sorry. mum.
I don't know
where those moves came from.
I tried to keep my heart rate down.
I fell at the first hurdle.
I banged my head.
I did a roly-poly.
My heart rate peaked.
I'm in love.
I am really going to try
and set pulses racing.
I've got a big fork as well.
Maybe I can stab one of them...
Wes. no. I'm joking.
Oh. hell.
Just trying to put my body
in their face.
Women can control men through sex.
(LAUGHS)
Laura went in!
I am so sweaty.
Well done.
The whole idea of this game
is to keep your heart rate down.
That was a struggle.
Hi. boys.
I'm here to take your temperature.
It wasn't really my sort of thing.
Credit to Grace.
not everyone is comfortable
doing this kind of thing.
That's fine.
She gave it her best shot.
I hope that I get pulses racing.
It will be embarrassing if I don't.
In my head. I look like Beyonce.
But in real life it's...
it's not going great.
She was looking unreal.
I am losing my mind.
People think that I am going to
be fantastic because I am a dancer.
Honestly. I don't do freestyle.
I could see a few of the boys' eyes
going "Oh my God."
Our tactic was deep breaths
and think of wallpaper.
That went out the window.
(APPLAUSE)
This is Megan.
I love the song!
The pressure is on.
It's hard to be sexy on demand.
I didn't know what came over me.
For Christ's sake.
What the hell just happened?
Did you? (LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS) Wes. I thought I
might as well go full force.
Jack is really enjoying it too much.
Are you kidding me?
Hi. boys!
My heart is racing for them.
I was scared!
I didn't know what to do
with my pom-poms!
I didn't know what
to do with them!
I am playing the game.
You are not playing the game.
Dani is not coming on here
and grinding on all my mates.
I love cheerleaders.
We are keeping those pom-poms.
Looking forward to that.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
She's so cute. man.
Hi. boys!
She's going to be all over Jack.
Oh my God.
I kept my lips like this.
It is a laugh It's banter.
If that is payback.
give me more. I saw a lot of booty.
Speechless. I am just speechless.
That was the hardest test
of my life.
Georgia pulled it off. She was
the best for me. I enjoyed it.
I have never seen Alex
smile so much.
So. now is the boys' turn.
First up is Josh.
Trousers came off. surprise!
I saw heart rates go up.
it was like a machine gun.
I kept it moving. I made sure Kaz
got the full show.
I could feel my heart rate being
like that! I couldn't hold it in.
I need a new profession. I am
going to be an exotic dancer.
I don't know what has happened.
that wasn't me. Jokes.
Jack picked me up and
threw me about! It was really good.
I definitely felt my heart
rate quicken.
I am trying to win this competition.
I don't care what it takes.
I don't even know what was going on.
Samira was the main target.
He has got the hip flexors.
Those thrusts must have broken
his back.
My heart rate went up!
That was one of the scariest and
weirdest things I have ever done.
Charlie was definitely the best
performer. He works it.
Charlie keeps surprising me.
Off! Off!
What have I just done?
Sam special! The girls did not know
where to look.
He was like a little squirrel.
Like he was doing interpretive
dance. It was too much.
Who is it?
It's Alex.
My heart rate was going a lot
quicker than when the girls danced.
Alex was like pouting. (LAUGHS)
I smouldered.
I did a bit of hip thrusting.
Bless him. he did so well.
Trying to have
a bit of fun with it.
It is the first and last time
you will ever see Alex stripping.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE)
Hero.
Aww!
I'll work any day over that.
I am not letting him win.
I was absolutely shitting myself.
Jack was funny. bless him.
I knew he would find it hard!
He is not the best dancer.
15 stone of south-east London beef.
Why have you got water?
Oh my God.
Obviously. wanted Megan to feel
a bit. Gave her an extra kiss.
Wes was hot as fuck. Even when
he was dancing with other girls.
That body.
He is pretty good at it. He has got
the rhythm. You are born with it.
Left the best till last.
What a nightmare.
We have got our BAFTA clips sorted.
The results are in.
Boys. Alex. your heart was raised
the most by Megan.
Everyone.
Jack. your heart was
raised the most by Georgia.
You want to see my face?
(LAUGHS)
I didn't even touch you. babe.
Sam. your heart was raised the most
by Georgia.
Josh. your heart was raised
the most by Georgia.
I think that was the nerves.
New Jack. your heart was raised
the most by Georgia.
Georgia was doing something right.
She also sent Frankie and Wes's
heart rate soaring.
Charlie's BPM went through the roof
for Kaz.
Kaz. your heart was raised the most
by Josh.
Samira. yours was by Wes.
It's the trousers.
Grace. your heart was raised
the most by Jack.
It works for someone.
My heart was raised the most
by old Jack.
George's heart rate
was raised the most by Wes
while Ellie and Megan were both sent
wild by Frankie.
Charlie's moves got Laura's heart
pumping.
Who out of the boys
or girls came out on top?
The team that raised the opposing
team's heart rate the most
was the boys.
We should all start a business.
They were worthy winners.
I'll be honest.
Frankie gave me a mild coronary.
On Sunday night...
..more trouble brewing for the girls.
I'll forgive her.
but I won't forget.
Georgia is all about Georgia.
I don't like her. I don't want
to have small talk with her.
subtitles by Deluxe
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm